Drew Holbrook

Profile

I'm a software engineer based in Crested Butte, Colorado. I'm the co-creator of Ekko, a self deployable realtime infrastructure with in-transit message processing that was built with a team of fully remote software engineers. I have multiple years of experience with the Ruby and Javascript ecosystems and am comfortable with AWS and Docker.

Skills

Backend	Frontend	Tooling	Cloud
Node.js, Express, Ruby,	JavaScript (ES6)	Git/GitHub, Docker, Linux	AWS, Digital Ocean,
Go, PostgreSQL, SQL,	React/Redux		Heroku
MongoDB, RESTful APIs	HTML/CSS		

Professional Experience

2021 – present	Co-Creator,	Software	Engineer
2021 – bresent	Co-Creator,	, Suitware	Eligilleer

Ekko 🛮

- Co-created Ekko, a self deployable realtime infrastructure with in-transit message processing
- Built websocket server using Node.js, socket.io, and Redis
- Designed AWS infrastructure (Application Load Balancer, ECS Fargate, S3, Elasticache, Lambda)
- Assisted in automating infrastructure deployment with AWS Cloud Development Kit
- Built CLI tool for infrastructure deployment, teardown, and Lambda management
- Load tested the real-time service using artillery.io to simulate 50,000 concurrent connections
- Collaborated daily with a team of fully remote engineers
- Co-authored Ekko's case study: https://ekko-realtime.com/

2018 – 2021 Full-Stack Web Developer

Self Employed

- Requestbin: Clone of popular tools to capture and store lists of incoming HTTP requests using Node.js, Express, and postgreSQL
- Shopping Cart: App with React/Redux font-end, Node.js, Express, MongoDB REST API backend
- Reaction: Trello-like app with React/Redux font-end, Node.js, Express, MongoDB REST API backend

2015 – 2018 Director of Marketing and Development

Crested Butte Nordic ☑

Helped grow revenue by 25% over three years

2014 – 2015 Director of Events

Crested Butte Nordic ☑

• Managed over 100 volunteers and organized events for more than 1000 participants

Education

2018 – 2021 **Launch School** ☑

A mastery based curriculum focused on the fundamentals of software engineering.

2004 - 2008

B.A. Economics

University of Vermont ☑